megapersonals.com 2011-12-23

# Mega Personals in Cary, USA

MegaPersonals.com PRIVACY POLICY

## PRIVACY POLICY

**[MegaPersonals.com](http://megapersonals.com/)** offers you a FREE forum for posting information about yourself and advertising yourself or your services.

By posting any information on the world wide web, including this Website, you understand that such information becomes accessible to anyone searching the web, including search engines and other forms of gaining information (known or yet to be discovered) and that such information may continue to exist for an unlimited or unknown period of time, even after it has ceased to appear on this Website. 

Some information we obtain from you is not available to the general public and is explained below.

### Our Commitment 

We take your privacy seriously. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about your personal information. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our web site including where personally identifiable information may be submitted. 

### What this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of all personally identifiable information collected or submitted on our site and your use of our services including ordering subscriptions, user feedback submissions, surveys, making requests or registering to receive materials from time to time. This Privacy Policy also covers our treatment of all personally identifiable information that our business partners share with us. 

### Information Collection and Use 

  * We collect personally identifiable information when you subscribe for our site and when you communicate with us about your subscription. 
  * When you subscribe or communicate with us, we ask for your email address and you are automatically added to a list of email recipients who receive information about related specials, updates, promotions, new products and services. 
  * We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, "cookie" information and the web page(s) you requested. 
  * We use information for three general purposes: (i) to customize the web content you see, (ii) to fulfill your requests for services, and (iii) to contact you regularly about related specials, updates, promotions, new products and services. 

### Unsubscribe

If you do not wish to be contacted regularly about related specials, updates, new products and services, you may unsubscribe from the list of email recipients by entering your email at <http://www.megapersonals.com/unsubscribe>. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * We may amend this policy from time to time. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. 

### Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place reasonably appropriate procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

### How You Can Correct Your Information 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows an error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections. 

### How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please send us an email at [Support@MegaPersonals.com.com ](mailto:Support@MegaPersonals.com.com)
